A Guide to the University Relations, Office of Information Services, Press Releases from William H. Wranek, Jr., 1921-1961, n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University Relations Office of Information Services, Press Releases from William H. Wranek, Jr. 1921-1961, n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/2/2.491
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the University Library in 1949-1976.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the Office of Information Services, Press Releases from William H. Wranek, Jr.
Contents List
- Press Releases 1921-1933, (7 folders) (Box 1)
- Press Releases 1933-1934, (6 folders) (Box 2)
- Press Releases 1934, (7 folders) (Box 3)
- Press Releases 1934-1935, (6 folders) (Box 4)
- Press Releases 1935-1939, (7 folders) (Box 5)
- Press Releases 1940-1948, (7 folders) (Box 6)
- 125th Anniversary 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Athletics 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Bibliographical Society 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Cavalier Daily 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Concerts 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Conferences at the University 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Conferences at the University 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Development Fund 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Easter Dances 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Education, Department of 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Engineering, Department of 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Engineering Extension 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Entering Students 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Expansion Releases 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Extension 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Faculty Releases 1949-1950 (Box 7)
- Finals 1949-1950 (Box 8)
- Fluid Mechanics 1949-1950 (Box 8)
- Founder's Day 1949-1950 (Box 8)
- Garden Week 1949-1950 (Box 8)
- General Information 1949-1950 (Box 8)
- General 1949-1950 (Box 8)
- Glee Club and Orchestra 1949-1950 (Box 8)
- Home Town Stories 1949-1950 (Box 8)
- Honor Societies 1949-1950 (Box 9)
- Institute of Public Affairs 1949-1950 (Box 9)
- Law School 1949-1950 (Box 9)
- Library 1949-1950 (Box 9)
- Medicine; Music 1949-1950 (Box 9)
- Miscellaneous 1949-1950 (Box 10)
- Prizes 1949-1950 (Box 10)
- Religion 1949-1950 (Box 10)
- ROTC 1949-1950 (Box 10)
- Societies 1949-1950 (Box 10)
- Theater 1949-1950 (Box 10)
- Dean's Lists 1951 (Box 10)
- Swanson Case 1951 (Box 10)
- Finals 1951 (Box 10)
- Fraternities 1951 (Box 11)
- Honor Societies 1951 (Box 11)
- Law School 1951 (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous 1951 Feb-Dec, (8 folders) (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous 1951-1954, (2 folders) (Box 12)
- Press Releases 1953-1955, (11 folders) (Box 13)
- Press Releases 1955-1957, (6 folders) (Box 14)
- Press Releases 1957-1961, n.d., (7 folders) (Box 15)